Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: Sh-Wh, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 6:1-275)
      - Correspondence from A. B. West, Cambria, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:245)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. E. West, Suffolk, Virginia, 1918., 10 items. (Box-folder 6:246)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Weymouth, Hampton, Virginia, 1914-1932., 9 items. (Box-folder 6:247)
      - Correspondence from O. J. Wharton, Baltimore, Maryland, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:248)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Clarence W. Whealton, Salisbury, Maryland, 1932-1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:249)
      - Correspondence from D. J. Whealton, Salisburg, Maryland, 1911-1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 6:250)
      - Duplicate correspondence to D. T. Whealton, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:251)
      - Correspondence from John B. Whealton, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:252)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Wayne B. Wheeler, Washington, D.C., 1927., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:253)
      - Correspondence from Whispering Pines Motor Company, Accomac, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:254B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. C. Whitaker, Poplar Hall, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:254B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the White Company, Wilmington, Delaware, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:255)
      - Correspondence from B. D. White, Norfolk, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:256)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. C. C. White, Mathews, Virginia, 1918, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 6:257)
      - Correspondence from Elizabeth White, Leesburg, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:258)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. G. White, Quinby, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:259)
      - Correspondence from Harry White, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:260A)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry E. White, Baltimore, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:260B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry T. White, Makemie Park, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:261)
      - Correspondence from J. Edward White, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:262A)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Louise White, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:262B)
      - Correspondence from M. F. White, Spotsylvania, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:263)
      - Correspondence from N. C. White, Keller, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:264)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rooker J. White, Keller, Virginia, 1912, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:265)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Roy D. White, Parsley, Virginia, 1922, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:266)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. B. F. White, Richlands, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:267)
      - Correspondence from W. F. White, Onley, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:268)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Will Robins White, Marsh Market, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:269)
      - Telegram from Willis G. White, South Boston, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:270)
      - Correspondence from E. F. Whitefield, Franklin, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:271)
      - Correspondence from Joseph A. Whitehead, Washington, D.C., 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:272)
      - Duplicate correspondence to M. Halsey Whitelaw, Winter Park, Florida, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:273)
      - Correspondence from E. P. Whitman, Pulaski, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:274)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with F. E. Whitt, Tazewell, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:275)
    - General Correspondence: Wi-Z, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 7:1-78)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John J. Wicker, Jr., Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:1)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Emma H. Wight, Winchester, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:2)
      - Correspondence from Wilber Mercantile Agency, Chicago, Illinois, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:3)
      - Correspondence from George E. Wiley, Bristol, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:4)
      - Duplicate correspondence with Captain Webb Wilkerson, Sanford, Virginia, 1924-1929., 8 items. (Box-folder 7:5)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Irvin G. Wilkins, Hilton Village, Virginia, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:6)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John T. Wilkins, III, Eastville, Virginia, 1910, 1928-1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:7)
      - Correspondence from S. S. Wilkins, Birds Nest, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:8)
      - Correspondence from W. E. Wilkins, Bridgetown, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:9)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas H. Wilcox, Norfolk, Virginia, 1920-1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:10)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Alfred Willett, Lee Mont, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:11)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Maurice B. (Hallie) Willett, Columbus, Ohio, 1934-1935., 10 items. (Box-folder 7:12)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. P. Williams, Norfolk, Virginia, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:13)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Ennion G. Williams, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:14)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Franklin K. Williams, Vienna, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:15)
      - Correspondence from Hugh T. Williams, Danville, Virginia, n.d., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:16)
      - Correspondence from J. E. Williams, Virginia Polytechnic, Blacksburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:17)
      - Correspondence from John B. Williams, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:18)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John W. Williams, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Leminel Williams, Horsey, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:20)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with T. F. Williams, Keller, Virginia, 1911-1912., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:21)
      - Correspondence from W. D. Williams, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911-1912., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:22)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. Holman Willis, Roanoke, Virginia, 1922, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:23)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Larry Wimbrow, Salisbury, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:24)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. W. Winder, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1923, 1930., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:25)
      - Correspondence from L. L. Winder, Elizabeth City, North Carolina, 1911., 8 items. (Box-folder 7:26)
      - Duplicate correspondence to L. A. Wingo, Baltimore, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:27)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. Arthur Winn, Port Haywood, Suffolk and Norfolk, Virginia, 1911-1929., 25 items. (Box-folder 7:28)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with B. K. Winston, Dillwyn, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:29)
      - Correspondence from P. Wilsher, Detroit, Michigan, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:30)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Eugene S. Wilson, New York City, New York, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:31)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. W. Wilson, Raven, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:32)
      - Duplicate correspondence from the John T. Wilson Co., Richmond, Virginia, 1921., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:33)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Victor P. Wilson, Hampton, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:34)
      - Correspondence from W. B. Wilson, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:35)
      - Correspondence from E. S. Wise, Craddickville, Virginia, 1912., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:36)
      - Correspondence from Henry A. Wise, Jonesville, South Carolina, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:37)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. and Mrs. Henry A. Wise, Kiptopeake, Virginia, 1929-1933., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:38)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry A. Wise, Parksley, Virginia, 1931-1933., 5 items. (Box-folder 7:39)
      - Correspondence from J. B. Wise, Cheriton, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:40)
      - Correspondence from Jennings S. Wise, Richmond, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:41)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Melvin Witham, Sanford, Virginia, 1924-1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:42)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Frank Witten, Tazewell, Virginia, 1925-1929., 17 items. (Box-folder 7:43)
      - Correspondence from W. E. Wolfenden, Roanke, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:44)
      - Correspondence from J. Edwin Wood, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:45)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. W. Wood and Son, Richmond, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:46)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Amos W. Woodcock, Salisbury, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:47)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. B. Woodfin, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:48)
      - Correspondence from J. F. Woodhouse, Princess Anne, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:49)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John Thomas Woodhouse, London Bridge, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:50)
      - Correspondence from Clifton A. Woodrum, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:51)
      - Correspondence from E. Woods, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:52)
      - Correspondence from Samuel B. Woods, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:53)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Marie Woodward, Suffolk, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:54)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Wyatt F. Woodward, Barhamsville, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:55)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Worchester Democrat, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:56)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Worchester Salt Co., 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:57)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. E. Worrell, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:58)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the Worthams of Hanover, Virginia, 1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:59)
      - Correspondence to G. C. Wright, Newport News, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:60)
      - Duplicate correspondence to G. H. Wright, New Church, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:61)
      - Correspondence from G. L. Wright, Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:62)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William A. Wright, Tappahannock, Virginia, 1926, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:63)
      - Telegram from W. J. Wright, Norfolk, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:64)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. L. Wyatt, Newport News, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:65)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. P. Wyatt, Crisfield, Maryland, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:66)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Paul Xenos, St. Paul, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:67)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Roxana Yancy, Moorestown, New Jersey, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:68)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the York Safe and Lock Co., Baltimore, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:69)
      - Correspondence from B. C. Young, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:70)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Doris Young, Justiceville, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:71)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John Young, Berlin, Maryland, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:72)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lottie Young, Accomac, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:73)
      - Correspondence from S. S. Young, Sr., Butterworth, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:74)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Warner K. Young, Bloxom, Virginia, 1918-1927., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:75)
      - Correspondence from B. Zimbler, Baltimore, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:76)
    - General Correspondence: Unknown or Unidentifiable Correspondents, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 6:77-78)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with unknown or unidentifiable correspondents, 1910-1924., 28 items. (Box-folder 7:77)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with unknown or unidentifiable correspondents, 1925-1932 and n.d., 31 items. (Box-folder 7:78)
  - Correspondence Pertaining to the 1914 Statewide Prohibition Election, 1895-1935. (Box-folder 7:79-99)
    Arrangement is alphabetically by county.
    - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County, 1914. (Box-folder 7:79-81)
      - Accomac County: A-H, 1914., 18 items. (Box-folder 7:79)
      - Accomac County: J-P, 1914., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:80)
      - Accomac County: R-W, 1914., 16 items. (Box-folder 7:81)
    - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County, 1914., 22 items. (Box-folder 7:82)
    - Correspondence with residents of Elizabeth City County, 1914., 25 items. (Box-folder 7:83)
    - Correspondence with residents of Essex County, 1914., 27 items. (Box-folder 7:84)
    - Correspondence with residents of Fredericksburg, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:85)
    - Correspondence with residents of Gloucester County, 1914., 7 items. (Box-folder 7:86)
    - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County, 1914., 16 items. (Box-folder 7:87)
    - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County, 1914., 17 items. (Box-folder 7:88)
    - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County, 1914., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:89)
    - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County, 1914., 11 items. (Box-folder 7:90)
    - Correspondence with residents of Newport News, 1914., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:91)
    - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County, 1914. (Box-folder 7:92-93)
      - Northampton County: A-L, 1914., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:92)
      - Northampton County: M-Z, 1914., 26 items. (Box-folder 7:93)
    - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County, 1914., 14 items. (Box-folder 7:94)
    - Correspondence with residents of Richmond County, 1914., 13 items. (Box-folder 7:95)
    - Correspondence with residents of Spotsylvania County, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:96)
    - Correspondence with residents of Warwick County (Denbigh), 1914., 10 items. (Box-folder 7:97)
    - Correspondence with residents of Westmoreland County, 1914., 28 items. (Box-folder 7:98)
    - Correspondence with residents of York County, 1914., 12 items. (Box-folder 7:99)
  - Correspondence Relating to the 1918 Congressional Democratic Primary, 1918. (Box 7-8)
    Folders 100-103 contain miscellaneous material relating to the 1918 Congressional Democratic Primary. Material includes precinct lists, lists of voters, results of the primary, and telegrams.
    Arranged alphabetically by county.
    - Lists of precincts, by county, in the 1st Congressional District of Virginia, 1918., 15 items. (Box-folder 7:100)
    - Mapp's typed lists of voters, by county, in the 1st Congressional District, 1918., 25 items. (Box-folder 7:101)
    - Assorted results of the August 6, 1918 Democratic primary for the 1st District Congressional seat, 1918., 27 items. (Box-folder 7:102)
    - Telegrams pertaining to the 1918 1st District Congressional election, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:103)
    - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918. (Box-folder 7:104-131)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: A, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:104)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Ba, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 7:105)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Be-Bu, 1918., 33 items. (Box-folder 7:106)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: By, 1918., 26 items. (Box-folder 7:107)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: C, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:108)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Da-Do, 1918., 9 items. (Box-folder 7:109)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Dr, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:110)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: E-G, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:111)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Ha-Hi, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 7:112)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Ho-Hy, 1918., 14 items. (Box-folder 7:113)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: J, 1918., 16 items. (Box-folder 7:114)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: K, 1918., 11 items. (Box-folder 7:115)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: L, 1918., 8 items. (Box-folder 7:116)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: M-Mas, 1918., 16 items. (Box-folder 7:117)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mat., A-Mat., S, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:118)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mat., W-May, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 7:119)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mea, A-H, 1918., 5 items. (Box-folder 7:120)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mears, James E., 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 7:121)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mears, John-Mei, 1918., 5 items. (Box-folder 7:122)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Mi-Mo, 1918., 14 items. (Box-folder 7:123)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: N, 1918., 17 items. (Box-folder 7:124)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: P, 1918., 14 items. (Box-folder 7:125)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Q-R, 1918., 13 items. (Box-folder 7:126)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: S, 1918., 30 items. (Box-folder 7:127)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: T, 1918., 17 items. (Box-folder 7:128)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Wa, 1918., 10 items. (Box-folder 7:129)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: We, 1918., 9 items. (Box-folder 7:130)
      - Correspondence with residents of Accomac County: Wh-Wi, 1918., 23 items. (Box-folder 7:131)
    - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918. (Box-folder 7:132-139)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: Be-Bo, 1918., 10 items. (Box-folder 7:132)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: Br, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 7:133)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: Bu, 1918., 8 items. (Box-folder 7:134)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: C, 1918., 14 items. (Box-folder 7:135)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: D-G, 1918., 12 items. (Box-folder 7:136)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: H-L, 1918., 17 items. (Box-folder 7:137)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: M-S, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 7:138)
      - Correspondence with residents of Caroline County: T-W, 1918., 12 items. (Box-folder 7:139)
    - Correspondence with residents of Elizabeth City, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Correspondence with residents of Essex County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 58 items. (Box-folder 8:2-4)
      - Correspondence with residents of Essex County: B-H, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:2)
      - Correspondence with residents of Essex County: L-P, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:3)
      - Correspondence with residents of Essex County: R-W, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Correspondence with residents of Fredericksburg, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 79 items. (Box-folder 8:5-7)
      - Correspondence with residents of Fredericksburg: A-F, 1918., 26 items. (Box-folder 8:5)
      - Correspondence with residents of Fredericksburg: G-J, 1918., 24 items. (Box-folder 8:6)
      - Correspondence with residents of Fredericksburg: M-W, 1918., 29 items. (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Correspondence with residents of Gloucester County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 77 items. (Box-folder 8:8-10)
      - Correspondence with residents of Gloucester County: A-B, 1918., 22 items. (Box-folder 8:8)
      - Correspondence with residents of Gloucester County: C-M, 1918., 27 items. (Box-folder 8:9)
      - Correspondence with residents of County: N-W, 1918., 28 items. (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Correspondence with residents of Hampton, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 84 items. (Box-folder 8:11-14)
      - Correspondence with residents of Hampton: B-C, 1918., 27 items. (Box-folder 8:11)
      - Correspondence with residents of Hampton: D-L, 1918., 16 items. (Box-folder 8:12)
      - Correspondence with residents of Hampton: M-T, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:13)
      - Correspondence with residents of Hampton: W, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:14)
    - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 54 items. (Box-folder 8:15-18)
      - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County: B-C, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 8:15)
      - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County: D-L, 1918., 17 items. (Box-folder 8:16)
      - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County: M-P, 1918., 15 items. (Box-folder 8:17)
      - Correspondence with residents of King and Queen County: R-V, 1918., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:18)
    - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 97 items. (Box-folder 8:19-22)
      - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County: B-E, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:19)
      - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County: F-J, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:20)
      - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County: L, 1918., 30 items. (Box-folder 8:21)
      - Correspondence with residents of Lancaster County: M-W, 1918., 26 items. (Box-folder 8:22)
    - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 147 items. (Box-folder 8:23-29)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: A-C, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 8:23)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: D-E, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:24)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: F-H, 1918., 33 items. (Box-folder 8:25)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: I-L, 1918., 26 items. (Box-folder 8:26)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: M-V, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 8:27)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: Wh, 1918., 19 items. (Box-folder 8:28)